<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<PMQuestions_Table>
  <question>
    <text>Mr Prime Minister, are we planning on a response to the growing crisis in the depreciation of the Euro against the Dollar?</text>
    <responses>
      <response>
        <text>Yes, I plan on talking extensively with our esteemed colleagues in the Eurozone, with the possibility of Aid.</text>
        <l>0.05</l>
        <c>0.025</c>
        <r>0.001</r>
      </response>
      <response>
        <text>I plan on providing no aid and am giving serious consideration to leaving the EU to better concern ourselves with our own affairs.</text>
        <l>-0.1</l>
        <c>-0.05</c>
        <r>-0.01</r>
      </response>
    </responses>
  </question>
  <question>
    <text>Mr Prime Minister, what are your thoughts with regards to my constituents in Burnley receiving inadequate support from our National Health Service?</text>
    <responses>
      <response>
        <text>This greatly concerns me and I fully intend to give my full support to my esteemed colleague who raised the question.</text>
        <l>0.05</l>
        <c>0.03</c>
        <r>0.01</r>
      </response>
      <response>
        <text>The NHS service is of great importance to the nation, but issues such as this clearly shows we must consider fundamental shifts in the health care of our nation.</text>
        <l>-0.1</l>
        <c>-0.05</c>
        <r>0.05</r>
      </response>
    </responses>
  </question>
  <question>
    <text>Mr Prime Minister, what is your response to my constituent's ongoing crisis with Council Tax being unaffordable for those on low income with families?</text>
    <responses>
      <response>
        <text>I am committed to seeing tax reforms that will benefit working class families, but we also need to commit to ensuring those same families have the social services they need</text>
        <l>0.03</l>
        <c>0.01</c>
        <r>0.01</r>
      </response>
      <response>
        <text>High taxes are causing a real struggle in working class families due to the atrocious budgeting of our predecessors. We are committed to reforms!</text>
        <l>0.0</l>
        <c>0.0</c>
        <r>0.05</r>
      </response>
      <response>
        <text>Why should working class families suffer paying high taxes when there are so many corporations and high earners dodging their fair share of taxes? This will be changed in our policy!</text>
        <l>0.1</l>
        <c>0.05</c>
        <r>-0.1</r>
      </response>
    </responses>
  </question>
  <question>
    <text>Mr Prime Minister, how do you respond to the media's reports of our beloved entertainer Mr Wright being turned away for a gay wedding ceremony?</text>
    <responses>
      <response>
        <text>While we support gay marriage, it is the right of every venue to only serve those who they wish to serve</text>
        <l>-0.03</l>
        <c>0.03</c>
        <r>0.07</r>
      </response>
      <response>
        <text>I am aware of a civil dispute arising from this, and we give our full support to Mr Wright.</text>
        <l>0.1</l>
        <c>0.05</c>
        <r>0.0</r>
      </response>
      <response>
        <text>This a tricky area, but we have to understand that marriage is an institution of historial note, and I am hesitant to change policy.</text>
        <l>-0.1</l>
        <c>-0.05</c>
        <r>0.05</r>
      </response>
    </responses>
  </question>
  <question>
    <text>Mr Prime Minister, how do you wish to address the ongoing problems in our educational system?</text>
    <responses>
      <response>
        <text>I think we need to take control of our state schools and form more academies, which are proven to raise grades.</text>
        <l>-0.05</l>
        <c>-0.01</c>
        <r>0.05</r>
      </response>
      <response>
        <text>We need to be concerned with forming valuable members of our society and we need to allow individual schools to take the decisions they know best to achieve this.</text>
        <l>0.03</l>
        <c>0.01</c>
        <r>-0.07</r>
      </response>
    </responses>
  </question>
</PMQuestions_Table>